Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ mauriciosotolongo (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

World Building 3D Modeling Texturing

Languages

English Spanish

Honors-Awards

Unreal Engine GDC Student Reel
Best of Ringling President's Award
Best of Ringling
RCAD Booth at GDC
Ringling Scholarship/Goldstein

Publications

Emerging Scholarship

Windrazor: First Take on Virtual Reality Games

How Naughty Dog Created the Immersive World of The Last of Us Part II

Mauricio Sotolongo

Senior Environment Artist at Meta

Miami, Florida, United States

Summary

Experienced Senior Environment Artist with a demonstrated history of working in the game development industry, as well as feature film, and arch-viz. High level of creativity and independence with strong foundational arts skills, and understanding of composition, form, color, lighting, film language, cameras, and VFX.

Experience

Meta

Senior Environment Artist July 2022 - Present (10 months) Miami, Florida, United States

Mountaintop Studios
Environment Artist
April 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 3 months)
Los Angeles, California, United States

Naughty Dog Environment Artist June 2019 - April 2021 (1 year 11 months)

Santa Monica, California

Buddha Jones 3D Artist September 2020 - November 2020 (3 months)

Bioware 3D Environment Artist July 2018 - May 2019 (11 months)

Austin, Texas

NeotradeVR 3D Generalist

June 2016 - August 2016 (3 months)

Miami, Florida, United States

Education

Ringling College of Art and Design

Game and Interactive Media Design · (2014 - 2018)

Miami Dade College Associate's Degree, Graphic Design · (2011 - 2014)